[theme music playing]
[Ivy] Everything will be over soon.
This town will finally be freed
from the Ardientes' grip.
[Julio] Relax, Arnaldo.
Nothing can stop your wedding.
[Arnaldo] Ivy's late, Grandpa.
What if she doesn't show up?
Calm, down, my son. Calm down.
She will be here.
[Diego] Jepoy, this isn't the
right time for you to interfere.
Ivy has plans.
What do you know about Ivy's plans?
-Everything.
-[Emilia] Are you in position?
Ready to fire once the bride arrives.
[grunts]
Make sure that Ivy Aguas
doesn't enter the church alive.
Your assassin's unconscious, Emilia.
[Emilia] If you think
I only hired one hitman,
then you're sorely mistaken.
[Ivy] I'm wearing black
because this is the only color
that suits this occasion.
[Emilia] Look how Ivy Aguas
is disrespecting us.
I can't let her do this to the family.
[Julio] What matters to me
is that she came
and that she will marry Arnaldo.
And, in a little while,
she will be an Ardiente.
Now, if she's got something bad planned,
she will suffer like everyone else
who does us wrong.
[Raul] Come to think of it,
that black gown suits her, Papa.
[Emilia] You're right, Raul.
It does suit her.
It's perfect for what
will happen to her later.
[tense music playing]
[priest] Let us all be seated.
We are gathered here today
to witness and celebrate
the very special love between Ivy Aguas
and Mayor Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo,
by joining them in marriage.
[sobbing]
[Anna] Auntie.
[Camia] Anna…
My daughter's marrying a monster!
Her life's in danger!
Auntie, Lily's smart. She can handle this.
She knows what she's doing.
We just have to have faith in her.
[sobbing]
Please, don't cry.
Of course, you have the right
to be angry, to be worried.
But Diego and Jepoy are there.
I'm sure they won't let
anything bad happen to Lily.
Let's just follow her plans, Auntie.
Besides, you're safer here.
Hush now.
Don't cry anymore.
[priest] If anyone has reasons
why Ivy and Arnaldo
should not be married,
speak now or forever hold your peace.
[tense music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Emilia] If you think
I only hired one hitman,
then you're mistaken.
If Ivy Aguas happens
to enter the church alive,
what makes you think
she'll get out alive too?
[Diego] You won't win today, Emilia.
-Ivy won't die.
-[beeping sound]
[suspenseful music playing]
[priest] In that case,
let's proceed with the ceremony.
[suspenseful music playing]
[beeping sound]
[beeping continues]
[ominous music]
[beeping]
Sorry, my dear Ivy.
You played the game a bit too well.
So now, it's your turn to get killed.
I'm ready to cry my fake tears for you.
I'm still the queen
of the Ardiente family.
And I will never, ever surrender my crown
to an ambitious nobody like you.
[bomb beeping]
[priest] Today is a celebration of love.
[suspenseful music]
And love alone is not enough
to make a marriage last.
It's important for a couple to follow
and respect the laws of marriage.
And for their families
to guide and support them.
It is also important to understand,
accept, forgive, and trust one another.
[beeping continues]
[priest] Love each other,
even when it hurts.
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[beeping continues]
[priest] Love even when
it is impossible to love.
[beeping continues]
[suspenseful music playing]
[explodes]
-[crowd exclaiming]
-[bomb explodes]
Ivy.
[unsettling music playing]
[fire crackling]
[Claire] Julio…
Are we under attack?
No, we're not under attack.
[suspenseful music playing]
What's that?
-You're one of Emilia's hitmen.
-No--
[grunting]
Ladies and gentlemen, please…
Please, don't panic.
You don't have to rush out of the church.
That explosion you just heard
was part of my surprise
for Ivy and Arnaldo's reception later.
So, there's nothing to worry about.
Everything is under control. So, please…
Sit down, please.
I'm guaranteeing this.
Nothing bad happened.
Who else is there?
[grunts]
[grunting]
How many are you here?! Tell me!
-Answer me!
-It's just me!
-Just you?!
-I swear!
[Jepoy] Yeah, right.
You mean you're going
to kill Ivy on your own?
[man grunting]
[panting]
[tense music playing]
Uh…
Continue with the ceremony, please.
Sorry about that.
Everything's okay.
[foreboding music playing]
Sit down.
If you were the ones
behind that explosion,
well, there's nothing you can do
to stop the inevitable.
I spent so long working on this plan.
I made a lot of sacrifices.
I even compromised my humanity
just to get to where I am today.
All for the sake of justice.
This plan cannot fail. I will succeed.
Ma'am Camia?
Uh…
-The wedding's in chaos.
-What?!
[reporter] An explosion
sparked tension at the church
where the wedding between
Mayor Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo
-and Ivy Aguas is being held.
-Loring, where's Diego?
-Call him.
-[Loring] Hold on.
[line ringing]
[news report on TV continues]
-[line ringing]
-Diego's not picking up.
-[Pandoy] What?!
-[line continues ringing]
[woman on TV] We were just watching…
-So?
-…when something exploded!
[line continues ringing]
[woman on TV] Everyone started
running to the front!
Change the channel.
[reporter] Do you think someone
tried to sabotage the wedding?
[priest] Very well. Ivy and Mayor Arnaldo…
Together, as you light
this candle of unity…
you symbolize the flame
of your individual souls.
Joining to ignite
the partnership of marriage.
[inaudible]
[unsettling music playing]
[Diego panting]
As my family's beloved son,
I was raised to be a winner.
A leader, a conqueror.
I grew up getting whatever I wanted.
And then, you came along, Miss Aguas.
I remember the first time I saw you.
I was out hunting in the woods.
It's funny because I was a predator…
trying to catch my prey.
But you captured me instead.
Since that day, I made it
my life's mission
to make you fall in love with me.
[line ringing]
Are you done yet?
We're running out of time.
Arnaldo's reciting his vows!
[Arnaldo] You were a real challenge.
And you knew it.
[chuckles]
But I want you to know
that I enjoyed every second…
every minute of that chase.
[Jepoy] I ran into a sniper.
But he said he was the last one.
[Arnaldo] Seeing you
in this lifetime, Ivy, I…
already said to myself that…
no one can ever bring me down.
But you?
You brought me down my knees.
You're the woman who brought me down.
[inaudible]
But only because I proposed,
and you said yes.
And for that, I'm grateful.
Now…
we have a lifetime of love
and happiness ahead of us.
[ominous music playing]
I can't wait.
In the eyes of the law,
within this church…
and in front of the whole world…
[inaudible]
You are mine,
and I'm yours.
And I can't wait to spend
a lifetime with you.
And only death will tear us apart.
[tense music playing]
[priest] Ivy, I believe you also prepared
your wedding vow for Arnaldo.
Of course.
[foreboding music playing]
Diego, Ivy is about to recite her vows!
I know! Be patient!
Is everything still going as planned?!
Arnaldo…
This is the day
that I have been waiting for.
-[line ringing]
-Come on, answer your phone!
[Ivy] The moment I've always dreamed of…
Thank you for your love, Arnaldo.
You accepted me, and so did your family,
despite that fact that I am an orphan.
I lost my adoptive family early on.
But despite that, I am blessed.
Because I met…
I met Nanny Carlotta.
Diego! I can't wait any longer!
What happened to your plan?!
-I will finish Arnaldo off!
-[Ivy] Nanny Carlotta, who…
treated me as a daughter.
Nanny Carlotta…
…gave me everything.
She devoted her life to me…
up until her last breath.
[tense music playing]
That's why when I lost Nanny Carlotta,
my world was shattered.
Jepoy! What are you doing?!
-That's not gonna help Ivy!
-You're not helping either!
Can't you be more patient?!
We're waiting for nothing, Diego!
[Ivy] But fortunately…
you were there for me.
You were there for me
when I was devastated,
and the love you offered comforted me.
We need to do something now!
[Ivy] Arnaldo, thank you
for your understanding…
and for your honesty.
That's why today…
[clears throat]
I will make you feel…
my true and burning desire.
[foreboding music playing]
[sobbing]
[priest] Do you, Arnaldo,
take Ivy to be your lawfully wedded wife?
To share your life openly,
standing with her in sickness
and in health…
We can't just outright stop the wedding!
You saw their armed men!
They'll shoot at us!
What's your plan?!
[priest] In joy and in sorrow,
in hardship and in ease…
to cherish and love forevermore?
Do you promise
with all your heart and soul
to honor this vow, till death do you part?
[foreboding music playing]
Uh… I do.
I do.
[priest] Do you, Ivy,
take Arnaldo to be
your lawfully wedded husband?
To share your life openly,
standing with him
in sickness and in health…
[sobbing] No!
[priest] In joy and in sorrow,
in hardship and in ease…
To cherish and love forevermore?
[Jepoy] What now?!
[priest] Do you promise
with all your heart and soul
to honor this vow till death do you part?
[suspenseful music playing]
Well?!
[pants]
[suspenseful music playing]
[priest] Do you, Ivy, take Arnaldo…
to be your lawfully wedded husband,
to share your life openly,
standing with him
in sickness and in health…
in joy and in sorrow…
in hardship and in ease,
to cherish and love forevermore?
[suspenseful music playing]
[priest] Do you promise
with all your heart and soul
to honor this vow till death do you part?
[suspenseful music playing]
[sobs]
Hon?
Hey!
Diego!
[suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music continues]
Stop the wedding!
-Auntie, it's Diego!
-Is that Diego?
-Diego?
[suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music continues]
[Fernan] Stay calm, okay?
There are soldiers.
[Marlon] Let's be careful.
Sir, don't shoot!
We're unarmed!
-We're unarmed!
-We're just going to watch.
Relax, we're just going to watch.
[tense music playing]
What do you think you're doing?
[Arnaldo] Well?
Auntie…
[tense music playing]
What do you think you're doing?!
You insolent fool!
-[Fernan] Hey, we're unarmed!
-[Marlon] We're unarmed!
Don't shoot!
-Guys, be careful!
-Sir, you're not allowed here!
Let us pass, we just want to watch!
Don't shoot, we're just going to watch.
Let us in!
[unintelligible]
[clamoring]
Ivy, you can't marry that man!
Why? Who are you to stop us?
Who are you?
[suspenseful music playing]
The bullet-ridden body
of a 21-year-old woman
identified as Nimfa Naig
was found this morning.
The investigation is still ongoing
to find the perpetrator
of this heinous crime.
As of now, the authorities
are yet to name their suspects.
The police are also investigating
the possible motives for the murder.
[tense music playing]
The 43-year-old Carlotta Navarro
was found dead in an apparent suicide
inside the home of wealthy businesswoman
and known supporter
of the Ardientes, Ivy Aguas.
[sobs] Aunt Carlotta!
[reporter] It is said that
personal problems…
My Aunt Carlotta!
[reporter] …pushed her to commit suicide.
There are reports that
she was allegedly deep in debt.
-She's Aguas' foster mother.
-What's the meaning of--
Turn this off!
-No statement has been given…
-[stammers] What is this?
Turn this off! Turn this off!
[Arnaldo] You won't get
your money until I get Ivy.
Where is she? I want to see her.
I want to talk to her.
[Arthur chuckling]
[Arthur] That's not going to happen!
Give me my money first,
and then I'll tell you where she is.
[sobs]
Uh… I-- I said turn this off!
-Who's in charge here?!
-I am, sir.
-[Arnaldo] Then turn this off!
-Do something! Turn that off!
[woman] Sir, we can't do anything.
-Even if we turn this off…
-[Julio] What?!
…it's on a simultaneous feed
throughout all of Ardiente.
The live feed is coming
from the Ardiente TV stations,
not from our systems.
We have no control.
The whole town of Ardiente
is watching this.
-Who did this?! Huh?!
-[Raul] Arnaldo!
Who?! Tell me!
-Arnaldo. Arnaldo…
-Tell me who it is!
Tell me! Tell me!
[Julio] You're getting paid
so do something about this!
[both grunting]
-[suspenseful music]
-[Arnaldo] Fight! Fight back!
Thank you, Arthur.
[Arnaldo] Fight back! Come on! Fight back!
[Arnaldo] What do you think?
You think you can order me around?
You think you can bring me down
without a fight, huh?! No!
You're a nobody!
And I'm the mayor!
Keep that in mind!
[Arthur] I've got Ivy Aguas!
[Arnaldo] Well, I have you now!
I have your phone too!
I can order your accomplice to let Ivy go.
And I can kill you too.
[tense music plays]
I can easily kill you
and make it look
like you committed suicide,
just like I did to Carlotta.
[tense music playing]
[inaudible]
What?
[sobs]
Arnaldo!
[breathing heavily]
-You heard that?
-He killed her?
So it was him!
[overlapping chatter]
[tense music playing]
Or I can also pin the blame
on someone else…
just like how I framed Diego
when I killed Nimfa.
[tense music playing]
You killed my daughter!
[Arnaldo] What now, Arthur?
I always get what I want.
Arnaldo!
So give me back my fiancée
before I blow your brains out.
Turn that thing off! Turn it off!
Turn it off right now! Turn it off!
[guests exclaiming]
-I'll kill--
-[grunts]
[woman] Oh, my goodness!
Please calm down!
[clamoring]
[unintelligible]
[tense music playing]
This is all on you.
You planned all this.
Is it true?
[tense music playing]
Arnaldo, is that true?
Is it true that you killed Nanny Carlotta?
[suspenseful music]
[suspenseful music playing]
[breathing heavily]
-Ivy…
-Answer me.
Answer me!
Ivy, that's not true.
He's just trying to ruin us.
[stutters] This is all part
of Diego's plan.
He's just trying to ruin our wedding--
You're not answering my question.
Did you kill Nanny Carlotta?!
-Ivy…
-Don't touch me!
Did you kill Nanny Carlotta?!
[ominous music playing]
[muffled screams]
I'm in charge. I'm in charge.
I'm in charge.
Uh…
I'm in charge. I'm in charge.
It was an accident.
[suspenseful music playing]
[sobbing]
[overlapping dialogue]
That can't be! The mayor
wouldn't do such a thing!
It was an accident. It was an accident.
-It was an accident.
-You didn't--
-You didn't mean to?
-I didn't mean it.
It was an accident.
But you killed her?
Who did this to you?!
Tell me!
[suspenseful music playing]
So you really killed her?
Monster!
-I didn't mean it!
-You bastard!
[Ivy screams]
-Why did you kill her?! Why?!
-I didn't mean to!
-What did she do to you?!
Why did you kill her?!
-[guests exclaiming]
-Bastard!
-You monster!
-No, no…
You demon!
No, no, no, no!
-Why did you kill her?!
-It was an accident!
-I didn't mean it!
-Why?
[Arnaldo sobs] I didn't mean it!
-Ivy, please have mercy…
-You monster!
Why should I have mercy on you?!
Did you have mercy on her?!
You hanged her! You killed her!
-You heartless monster!
-[Arnaldo mumbling]
No, Ivy. Don't do this.
I love you so much!
Please forgive me!
[tense music playing]
Please, forgive me. Please… [sobs]
-Arnaldo!
-Please, forgive me. Please.
-This is humiliating!
-Forgive me, I'll do anything!
-Arnaldo, get up!
-Don't touch me!
-Stay out of this!
-[Emilia] Arnaldo!
Ivy, I'm sorry.
[sobs] Please, forgive me…
No, don't leave me. You love me, right?
I don't love you! I don't love you!
I'll never love a demon like you!
You're a demon!
-You said you love me!
-A monster! I don't love you!
-You love me! You love--
-I don't!
I'll never marry a demon like you!
You're a murderer! I will never love you!
-No! You love me! You love me!
-No!
-You're marrying me!
-Arnaldo!
We will get married!
You killed my daughter!
Let's go!
-You can't enter!
-Stop!
-You're marrying me!
-No!
-Arnaldo! Stop!
-[Emilia] Arnaldo!
-[Diego] That's enough!
-[Emilia] Arnald--
-[Fernan] He's a murderer!
-[Marlon] Let us in!
Murderer!
You can't enter!
[suspenseful music playing]
[man] Let's go, everyone!
-Stay here!
-You can't go inside!
[clamoring]
[Diego] It's time for you to pay
for all your crimes!
Arrest this man!
Take him to prison! Arrest Arnaldo!
Stop them! I said, stop them!
[suspenseful music playing]
-Stop them!
-Arnaldo!
Where are you taking him?!
[indistinct shouting]
[ongoing commotion on TV]
[inaudible]
[clamoring]
-[Diego] Get him!
-[Julio] Arnaldo!
[Diego] Arrest him now!
Take him!
-Ivy!
-[Raul] Let go of my son!
[clamoring]
[suspenseful music playing]
[inaudible]
[suspenseful music continues]
[music fading]
[somber music playing]
[Ivy] This is for my father.
For Mom.
[gunshot]
For Nanny Carlotta.
-For Nimfa.
-[gunshot]
For all those who were abused…
-and treated like animals.
-[gunshot]
For all those who suffered…
and died in the hands of the Ardientes.
[somber music playing]
This is all for you.
This is the justice I promised long ago.
[somber music playing]
[crowd clamoring]
-Excuse me.
-Mayor!
[Ivy] Impressive, Mendoza.
I'll transfer the money to your account,
but make sure to share it
-with the woman you hired.
-[Arnaldo screaming]
Make it stop! Make it stop!
-Hon! Hon!
-Make it stop!
[sinister music playing]
[Ivy] Slowly but surely,
my plans are unfolding.
But this isn't the end of it.
Diego, I need to talk to Arthur
as soon as possible.
Ready, Ivy?
Five, four, three, two… action!
Good morning, hon!
Go on, eat your breakfast.
I'll just go to the restroom.
[upbeat music playing]
[Arnaldo] Twenty million pesos?
Are you crazy?
If you're threatening me,
I'm not afraid of you.
How about I trace this call?
I'll hunt you down and kill you!
I will kill-- Hello? Hello?!
Hon? Who were you talking to?
My staff.
[Ivy] It's so hot, hon.
I'll go take a shower.
[upbeat music continues]
Anyway, hon, I'm sure we'll find Diego…
So--
[shower running]
[glass breaks]
Ivy?
[shower running]
[suspenseful music playing]
-Thank you!
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
-[phone rings]
-[phone ringing]
-Who's calling?
-Your mother.
-Don't let her know.
Hello, Auntie? Yes, I'm on my way back.
I just had an important matter
to attend to.
Yes.
You better get going before
they suspect anything.
Thank you, Diego.
Hello?
Do you want to get Ivy Aguas back?
Damn you! What do you want from me?!
Face me by yourself.
No Ardientes. No cops.
No pesky media.
Or else…
Ivy Aguas will die.
Who do you think you are?
Do you think you can just order me around?
You're a nobody!
And I'm the mayor! Remember that!
I can easily kill you
and make it look like
you committed suicide…
just like what I did to Carlotta.
Or I can also pin the blame
on someone else,
just like how I framed Diego up
when I killed Nimfa.
So, don't mess with me.
Never mess with me!
[tense music playing]
-Sir, please don't shoot!
-Hands up!
Don't worry. We won't hurt you.
The bullet-ridden body
of a 21-year old-woman…
[Ivy] Now you know
how Ivy Aguas exacts her revenge
-on devils like you!
-Ivy!
[unintelligible]
You better be ready, Emilia.
-[Diego] Arrest him!
-[Arnaldo] Ivy!
Arnaldo!
-[Diego] Hold him down!
-[Ivy] You're next on my list.
Ivy! Tell them I'm innocent!
You killed my daughter, you monster!
-[grunts]
-Stop it, you bastard!
That's enough! How dare you
do that to the mayor?!
Stop this!
As the congressman of this town,
I'm ordering you to stop this!
You bastards!
-Animals!
-[guests exclaiming]
[Arnaldo] Let go of my grandpa!
[all exclaiming]
[Emilia screaming] Papa!
[suspenseful music playing]
-Oh, no.
-[Pandoy] Diego!
[suspenseful music playing]
-This is all your fault!
-[Raul] Arnaldo!
[Emilia] Arnaldo!
[suspenseful music playing]
-Is this really happening?
-Get inside, kids.
That wedding is terrifying.
[all exclaiming]
Arnaldo!
You've always tried to ruin
everything in my life.
Everything!
You ruined everything, you bastard!
-Arnaldo!
-I'm going to finish you off!
[suspenseful music playing]
I'm going to end all this!
Arnaldo.
Go ahead, shoot.
Do it,
so that the people can see
who the Ardientes really are!
So that they will all wake up
and finally see the truth.
And I'm ready to give my life for change.
[suspenseful music playing]
Do it!
Do it! Shoot me!
-Do it!
-Diego! Wait!
Arnaldo! Drop the gun!
You're brothers!
[suspenseful music playing]
Arnaldo? Arnaldo!
[laughs]
-[laughs]
-[gunshot]
-[guests exclaiming]
-[gunshots]
[gunshots]
[gunshot]
[inaudible]
-[gunshot]
-Lily!
-Lily! My child!
-[gunshot]
[suspenseful music playing]
[sobs] Lily!
[Diego] Arrest him!
[people screaming]
[gunshots]
-[gunshots]
-[people screaming]
[Diego] Get him!
He's a criminal! Arrest him!
[suspenseful music playing]
Jepoy!
Help!
Hurry!
Ivy…
Let's take her to the hospital!
Hurry!
Jepoy, get a car!
Ivy…
Ivy.
Ivy, I'm right here.
We did it.
["Wildflower" by Arnel Pineda playing]
♪ Let her cry ♪
-Yay! We did it!
-♪ For she's a lady ♪
♪ Let her dream ♪
♪ For she's a child ♪
♪ Let the rain fall down ♪
♪ Upon her ♪
♪ She's a free and gentle flower ♪
♪ Growing wild ♪
♪ Let her cry ♪
♪ For she's a lady ♪
-♪ Let her dream ♪
-Ivy?
-♪ She's a child ♪
-♪ Let the rain fall down ♪
-Ivy!
♪ Upon her ♪
♪ She's a free and gentle flower ♪
♪ Growing wild ♪
Mom!
[clamoring]
[Julio] They've forgotten
who they're going up against.
We Ardientes know
how to manipulate the law.
[Camia] Ivy is Lily Cruz.
She is my daughter.
I'm the mayor here! Why am I in jail?!
You! You ruined our family!
[Diego] You'll rot in jail.
You will never get Ivy back.
-Ivy!
-Did you miss me?
-Yes.
-Screw you!
Say hi to Emilia for me.
Tell your mom that she's about
to get what she's looking for.
Ivy! Ivy!
This is all your fault!
It's all your fault!
[Raul] Arnaldo!
[Emilia] I can smell the traitor
in that Ivy Aguas, Papa.
She plotted everything
to bring Arnaldo down!
We should kill her!
[Julio] You were the golden boy
of our family.
How could you let your life
be ruined by a woman?!
Give me Ivy. Please, Grandpa…
Give me Ivy…
[Julio] Ivy Aguas' funeral is
postponed until further notice.
[screams]
I'm here to make you an offer, Ivy.
A hundred million pesos.
-In exchange for what?
-Get back together with my grandson.
[Camia] What are you going to do?
Are you going to help Arnaldo recover
after you tore him down?
[Ivy] Arnaldo is the weakness
of the Ardientes--
Emilia, Raul, and especially Julio.
So I need Arnaldo to finish off
the Ardientes once and for all.
Let the games begin.
Charges against Mayor
Arnaldo Torillo were dismissed.
[Camia] They've proven yet again
that they have the law at their disposal.
Arnaldo… Arnaldo!
-Arnaldo, enough!
-[chuckles]
You have to accept the fact
that Arnaldo is not well!
No one tells Julio Ardiente what to do!
I need to be with the Ardientes
so I can protect you.
Don't you dare go near my son!
We aren't done yet!
[Ivy] Death doesn't suit you.
You deserve something worse.
An Ardiente never loses.
An Ardiente never dies.
[maid] Ma'am Emilia!
[shrieking]
[theme music playing]